I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
Rocío Owono Durán. You're free to go.
Rocío's fine. She's been released.
You're not dressed yet?
My dad's gonna be pissed
if you don't come.
I don't give a shit.
Wait, what's that smell?
- What did you do?
- Leave me alone!
Where's your cousin?
Look. Enough is enough.
Dad, he's not okay today.
Let's just go, Alfonso.
He can skip class if he wants to.
It's best if we leave him be.
María, we can't just sit back
and let him do whatever he feels like.
Morning, family!
Good morning, honey. Are you feeling okay?
Yeah, Aunt María. Just great. Why?
Good morning.
ROCÍO: YOU COMING TO SCHOOL?
Welcome to the first
Pan-African Meeting for Excellence.
Hey, Chloe.
Las Encinas, as a member
of Excellentia Academic Global League,
is proud to present
its exchange scholarship program
with Africa's two best private schools.
The Lua Jean School in Maputo, Mozambique,
and the Parkhurst School
in Cape Town, South Africa.
This is thanks to an initiative
from the Catalina Durán
Hispanic-Pan-African Foundation.
I can't keep using my connections
to bail you out of trouble, Rocío.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Women like us
face triple the pressure in society.
I want a better world too.
That's why I'm a judge, not a squatter.
Use the education we're giving you
to get training and change things
in an intelligent and civilized way.
Your soccer uniform
and gala dress are in the trunk.
Take them and go inside.
Could I just skip today?
I'm exhausted. I need a shower.
You can shower and get changed at school.
Virginia and I have spent
too much time on this.
How's it going?
Morning.
I've been messaging you,
but you haven't texted back.
Do you need space?
Look, Iván, we said
we were gonna be friends.
And we can be friends and classmates
but live our own lives outside of school.
You talked to Omar?
See you in class.
Holy shit! What the hell?
Come down here a sec.
- Why?
- I wanna show you something.
Yeah, no.
You're getting on my nerves.
Please. Just for a second.
Okay.
I added it to your playlist.
Don't you get tired of pulling
cringey stunts to get my attention?
Says the girl who makes sex tapes.
All right.
I'm trying to get along with you,
but you're making it hard.
I never asked you to make an effort.
- That's awful. For real?
- Mm-hmm.
- I got arrested, and he did nothing.
- What's up with him?
After he saw me with Chloe,
he came home with cuts on his head.
And this morning, he was in a shit mood.
Five minutes later, he was totally fine.
Have you seen his semicolon tattoo?
I'm not sure. He's covered in marks. Why?
Come on, Rocío! Come on!
Is that your cousin?
Rocío!
Look, I want to keep my distance from him.
- I hope you understand.
- Sure. Don't worry.
Rocío!
Let's go, team!
Here! Pass it!
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Really?
I'm okay. Thanks.
I never thought a pickup game
could affect me this much.
You must've had an inkling.
Otherwise, you would've played.
Right?
I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T. I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
"TALK" REPORTS
Warning signs are present
in 90% of suicide attempts.
These aren't just cries for attention.
They're calls for help.
I'll share your report
with counseling department.
Is that all?
They're the experts, Omar.
You're not trained to handle this.
Was there anything else?
Yes.
I need a list of the scholarship students.
You know that's confidential.
Asshole.
I sent you the app login details
so you can reply
if you see anything out of the ordinary.
I can't do this alone,
and that idiot Luis isn't helping.
Is that why you haven't replied?
You don't think you can handle it?
And because I once said
those exact words myself.
It's too much for me.
How did you get help?
Omar?
Omar!
It's me. Joel.
From the association. Remember me?
Go away.
Omar, calm down, please.
Just go away.
Omar, look at me, okay?
I can't. No. I can't.
Omar, look at me, please.
Please.
Easy.
Please, Omar.
That's it.
That's good.
IF YOU CAN'T HANDLE IT ALL ALONE,
I'M HERE TO HELP.
I KEEP MISTREATING
THE PEOPLE WHO TREAT ME WELL.
I'M LONELY, AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
Their writing style looks familiar.
Want to handle it?
Do you think some people are just jerks?
That they're evil by nature?
I think some people suffer a lot.
SEMICOLON TATTOO
ANXIETY, DEPRESSION, SUICIDE ATTEMPT
Hey. I'm so sorry I let you down.
I get why you're avoiding me.
I was a coward.
Great. You apologized.
Thanks. See you around.
Don't be mad at me, please.
It's not like we're close.
I know, but we could be.
That moment we shared
at the squat was awesome.
Until it all went to shit.
Seriously, I gotta go.
I'm a shithead who lets everyone down.
That's why I always end up alone.
Eric, please.
If it's not disappointment,
what is it? Is it fear?
Is that it? Do I scare you?
Then say I scare you
and you're distancing yourself
'cause I'm not worth it.
Or 'cause you don't get me
and it scares you.
Just like my folks.
Better yet, don't say anything
so I'll realize that you weren't worth it.
Hey, Eric!
Eric, look at me! Breathe.
Breathe. Come on.
That's it.
All right. Easy. I'm here.
Luis.
ACCOUNT HOLDER: IVÁN CRUZ CARVALHO
LEAVE GROUP?
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
SARAUL.GOALS HAS HIGHLIGHTED A STORY.
You've seen plenty of bling tonight,
but this moment
is gonna shine the brightest.
Sara…
will you marry me?
Are you okay, baby?
Yes.
I think your boyfriend went too far
with that proposal, to be honest.
We're too young to settle down.
- How are things with Dídac?
- Fine.
I'm hanging in there,
still trying to get him out of my head,
but I'm okay.
Nothing a good party can't solve.
How is he?
He took the meds and went to bed,
but he was a wreck.
Nico! Still dressed like that?
- What do you mean?
- Everyone's at the party!
- Maybe you should stay in tonight.
- No way. I wanna hit the dance floor.
And the African kids are here.
We need to be good hosts.
- Listen to your aunt.
- Nico, come on.
We should stay in.
- Not coming? I'm out. See you.
- Eric, honey, wait.
Nico, darling, go with him.
- Keep an eye on him, please.
- He'll drag Nico down with him.
Don't worry, Dad. I'll be fine.
Do you have a better idea?
Are you serious?
Tell me you're not serious.
You know who they remind me of?
- Who?
- My parents when they fight.
Right.
My parents fight a lot too, to be honest.
Do you think you and I
will be like that in 20 years?
Hysterical, loud, and frustrated?
Look.
Society tries to trick us into thinking
that we should actually want to grow up.
But when you grow up,
life knocks you down,
and you go crazy, like those two.
Then all you want is
to be our age again and be immature.
Let's make the most of it while we can.
- What is it?
- I don't know. Let's see.
- Whoa.
- What?
- There's a problem with the music. Weird.
- No.
- I'll go fix it.
- Don't.
- Yeah. I'm gonna fix it. See you later.
- Yeah, from a distance.
- My God.
- I'll be right back.
- Calm down.
- You calm down, dammit!
You're doing a great job.
Excellent work, Cata. Thank you.
I'm sorry I rushed you.
Luena, don't go.
And so, they were winning…
There. Two hundred.
Count it, Catalina. We've got time.
I trust you.
But no more favors, Martín.
- You always say that.
- I mean it.
Expediting the eviction
meant my daughter got arrested.
I can't put myself at risk again.
She moved up the eviction date.
Find me judges named Catalina.
- We don't have permission.
- He's bribing her.
- Jesus.
- What?
She's the mother of one of the students.
Dídac, where are you?
What's taking you so long?
Are you still in my room? I'm coming up.
- I'd better go.
- Okay.
I can't believe this.
Dad! Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
- Hello, honey.
- Hi.
- I wanted to surprise you.
- How are you?
I love seeing
that look of surprise on your face.
I missed you so much.
- I'm so happy to be here.
- Hi, Isa.
- I'm heading out. I'll see you.
- All right.
You look amazing.
- Why was she here?
- I'll explain later.
It was about the scholarships.
This school costs a fortune,
and the parents take care of everything.
- It's crazy.
- Mom.
If I wanted a lie,
I'd ask you, but I asked Dad.
- See? She's so snippy with me.
- Can we please keep things civil?
Let's all have a drink together.
It's been too long.
- Please.
- Yeah. Way too long.
Come on. Let's go.
Our engagement is through the roof
since the announcement.
I mean, everyone is messaging us.
They're offering us serious money
for collaborations with the wedding.
JESSICA: SARA, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
AREN'T YOU COMING TO CLASS?
Hey, why's that teacher texting you?
Just class stuff.
This late at night?
I THINK IT'S BEST IF I DON'T.
What? Is she in love with you?
- Is that it?
- Don't be silly.
Here, to us.
Hi, guys!
- What's up?
- We're here with Saraul. Goals.
And the African students,
who are here to teach us
how to throw a killer party!
Hi, beautiful people!
Hi. See you later.
- All together!
- Have you seen this?
He wants to be an influencer now.
He's in for a major letdown.
An influencer?
The drinks, the lights, the music…
He has a few thousand followers,
and he says he can make a living out of it
if he works on it.
- Is he gonna quit his job?
- I sure hope not.
I can't cover his rent
while he's slacking and posting stories.
Iván!
I know I'm going about this all wrong.
And… I really…
I didn't want to hurt either of you.
But in the end, I'm hurting you both.
But I…
I need to do right by Omar.
Because I love him…
and I feel I'm… letting him down.
And we don't deserve that.
None of us do.
Work things out with him.
And tell him he's very lucky.
To big disappointments.
Or big discoveries.
- If you like him, why brush him off?
- I'm not brushing him off.
You so are.
But I'm not a romantic like you
who ends up doing shots with friends.
- Wanna dance?
- Okay.
Come on.
- Hey, I wanted to say-
- What?
What you looking at?
You.
Me?
How about you stop looking and kiss me?
What? Do you like it?
It's just what I needed.
Is it?
- You mean the shot or me?
- You.
What was it you needed?
I don't want someone
to remind me how worthless I am.
I want someone
who's as fucked up and insecure as I am.
You fucking prick.
Fuck. Asshole!
Gin, please.
Thanks.
Chloe.
- Chloe, what's wrong?
- Leave me alone.
Did he hurt you?
- No.
- What's wrong?
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
NEW MESSAGE
Want to go?
Yeah. Here.
Hey, Sara.
Do you think I'm a monster?
Why are you asking?
I know I have to change,
but I've always loved and protected you.
Yeah, I know that.
Are you sure?
Well, yeah.
What's this about?
Never mind.
Thanks for listening.
You know I'm always here for you, right?
Yeah. Thanks.
Chloe!
It's my mom. I should go.
Thank you.
Take care.
You're going to catch a cold, honey.
- Why are your eyes all puffy?
- It's nothing.
It's not nothing.
You look like a hound dog.
What happened?
Why were you hugging Iván and crying?
Baby, I hope you didn't-
What the hell, Mom? No way.
I mean, Iván's a great guy.
He listened to me
and was there for me. End of story.
I'm really glad to hear you say that.
I like to see the two of you connecting.
Mom, could you stop thinking
about your plan and think about me?
What plan? What are you talking about?
PEOPLE CARE BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT,
DEEP DOWN,
YOU HAVE A DAMAGED HEART THAT'S WORTH IT.
FIND IT AND NURTURE IT.
Hey, Chloe.
Chloe, say something.
Chloe, talk to me.
Iván wants to go on an exchange program
so he can start over.
Where?
South Africa.
- What?
- That's why we have to leave him alone.
He needs time and space
to find himself again.
The last thing he needs is a crazy mother
and a sister like me.
Put your seat belt on.
I can't find my cousin,
and I'm worried about him.
- It's so nice to be together as a family.
- We deserve it.
Let's try our best
to do this more often, okay?
I'm through making excuses.
What did I say earlier?
- You promise?
- Look.
- Like when she was little.
- We'll be seeing much more of each other.
- I believe you.
- Of course, honey.
I missed you.
I need to take care of something,
but I'll be back.
Can't you stay with us for a second?
She's always on the go.
Don't be long.
- Don't badmouth my dad.
- Are you listening?
- I am!
- I saw it go down, dammit!
Have you seen Eric?
- No.
Go on. Tell Rocío her mom's corrupt
and is in business with my dad.
- Enough with the secrecy.
- What?
Nothing. We didn't see him.
- What did you say about my mom?
- Nothing. I don't know.
- We're arguing.
- So why did you bring my mom into it?
Rocío, come on! We're arguing here.
I don't want to be rude to you!
- Why don't you believe me?
- Look, Dídac. I'm begging you.
That's enough.
I'm trying to keep it together.
What are you looking at?
INCOMING CALL: MOM
- Let go! You bastard!
- Easy.
- Motherfucker!
- What are you doing?
- Let go!
- He was throwing himself at the windows.
We had to restrain him.
Shit, Eric.
Leave me alone!
I don't get why you'd rather hurt yourself
than ask for help.
You're the one pushing us away.
Eric.
Nico, I have to go.
Do you think it's my fault
that people I care about abandon me?
No way.
How long will it take you?
It's so nice
that we can be together with your mom.
You need to cut her some slack.
Can you fix your outfit? Thanks.
She might make mistakes,
but she wants what's best for you.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Are you bribing Rocío's mom?
Nobody move! This is a police raid!
Please cooperate!
Shit.
Come with me.
Surprise.
Well, it's a little watery.
You're very quiet.
You really got a scholarship?
No.
Great.
How are you paying for your tuition?
Somebody offered to pay.
Somebody?
Who?
- In exchange for what?
- Nothing.
You answered the second question,
not the first.
It's fine.
I know it's Iván.
- Should I keep going?
- There's nothing more to it.
I think there is.
Are you in love with him?
I'm confused.
And I don't want to leave you.
Why?
Afraid I'll relapse?
So you'll stay in an unhappy relationship?
I'm not unhappy with you.
Joel, it's been days
since you've checked out.
- Go to him.
- What?
- What do you mean? No.
- Joel, really. Go to him.
No, Omar. I can't do this to you.
- It's what you want.
- I don't want that. I love you.
I love you too. But you don't need
to stay because you owe me.
If anything, I owe you.
You don't owe me either.
Okay, so nobody owes anybody.
No debt, just love.
And loving you means
I won't be the jerk holding you back.
Go to him.
Just go. I'll clean this up.
Jesus, Mom.
Mom.
What the hell are you doing?
Talking to Iván. He can't leave.
You're his mom, right?
Think about what's best for him.
He doesn't need you, Mom.
He doesn't need us. Not now.
Okay?
Come on. I said no.
Damn it.
- Hi.
- Hello, darling.
I'm here to thank you
for being so nice to Chloe.
It was nothing. She needed it.
See? You are a sweetheart. May we come in?
I'd like to talk to you
about something important.
- Is something wrong?
- No.
Can I tell you inside?
Yeah, sure.
Are you coming?
- Hi.
Why are you here?
Well, I came to see you,
but… if you're busy, it can wait.
No, not at all.
Come in. We were on our way out.
Mom, you and I are going home.
Hey. Are you okay?
Just so you know, it was one
of my best nights in a while too.
Let's go.
Iván deserves to enjoy this, okay?
I'm going to tell him, Chloe.
That's fine. But not today, okay?
Omar?
Omar!
Omar…
Oh my God. Omar.
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro,
Meredith Cannella